[{"id":1,"question":"When developing a backlink strategy, what approach would be most beneficial?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Guest post the article to as many sites as possible","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Create an infographics and share it with relevant bloggers","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Create diverse and unnatural links","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Distribute links in comment sections of websites","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":2,"question":"What is a key reason the URL `domain.com/apparel/jackets` is preferable to the URL `domain.com/p=141`?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"It is longer","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It is not preferable","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It uses structured markup","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It is readable to a human","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":3,"question":"Which HTTP response status code would indicate a page has been moved permanently?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"410","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"302","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"200","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"301","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":4,"question":"You notice a website is serving HTML to a Search Engine than to a human user. What is this an example of?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Spam injection","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Cloaking","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Sneaky Redirect","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Splicing","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":5,"question":"What would significantly improve Google&#39;s ability to a non-YouTube video in its Search Results?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Provide a 150 x 80 pixel thumbnail image","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Add Schema.org VideoObject","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Convert .mp4 videos to .mov","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Embed video objects with JavaScript conditionals","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":6,"question":"Google primarily determines indexing and ranking by crawling which version of a page?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Responsive version","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Submitted version","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Mobile version","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Desktop version","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":7,"question":"You want to identify which US state has the most search interest for a particular keyword. What tool would help you determine this?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Google Analytics","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Google Keyword Planner","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Google Search Console","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Google Trends","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":8,"question":"You want to block crawlers from accessing your entire website. What robots.txt entry would you use?","code":"markdown     User-agent: Allbots     Disallow: *  markdown     User-agent: /     Disallow: *  markdown     User-agent: /     Disallow:  markdown     User-agent: *     Disallow: /","choices":[{"text":"markdown\n    User-agent: Allbots\n    Disallow: *\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"markdown\n    User-agent: /\n    Disallow: *\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"markdown\n    User-agent: /\n    Disallow:\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"markdown\n    User-agent: *\n    Disallow: /\n","code":true,"answer":true}]},{"id":9,"question":"Which results is most likely if you use an interstitial pop-up that requires a user to take action before you load the content of the page?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Both the pop-up and the content of the page will be indexed","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The pop-up will be indexed instead of the desired body content","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"An interstitial pop-up is treated the same as a soft 404","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The pop-up will be ignored, and the content of the page will be indexed correctly","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":10,"question":"You notice a particular product in an e-commerce storefront is no longer indexed, despite no technical issues. What is a likely reason for this?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"No title or meta description tags were provided","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"The Keywords is too competitive","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Robots.txt is configured to allow access","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The product is out of stock","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":11,"question":"All bylone dates for articles are suddenly no longer visible on a `website&#39;s` listing within Google Search. Assuming no changes have been made to the site programming or content, what is the most likely cause?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"The site has been delisted from Google Search","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"A Google News sitemap was not provided within 30 days of setting up a publisher center account","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The site kept updating the dates to make the content appear fres, without changing","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The articles have aged more than 365 days without any significant updates to the content or the site","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":12,"question":"Which approach is not advisable to Geo-targeting your website?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Using a gTLD with subdomain","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"using URL parameters","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Using a ccTLD","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Using a gTLD with a subdirectory","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":13,"question":"You have been asked to help a big e-commerce brand optimize their website for search engines. They currently have thousands of products listed on their website. What is your most appropriate first step?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Recommend that they add more products","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Work on compressing image files","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"302 redirect all product pages to URL that contains target keywords","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Register the business with a Google My Business account.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":14,"question":"What Does The Term &quot;Sandbox&quot; Mean In SEO?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"The Box With Paid Ads That Appear When You Perform A Search.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"This Is Where Sites Are Kept Till They Get Mature Enough To Be Included In The Top Rankings For A Particular Keyword","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"A Special Category Of Sites That Are Listed In Kid-safe Searches","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The First 10 Search Results For A Particular Keyword.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":15,"question":"What Is Anchor Text?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"It Is The Main Body Of Text On A Particular Web Page","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It Is The Text Within The Left Or Top Panel Of A Web Page","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It Is The Visible Text That Is Hyper Linked To Another Page","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"It Is The Most Prominent Text On The Page That The Search Engines Use To Assign A Title To The Page","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":16,"question":"Which Google search query should be used to return only PDF documents that reference Microsoft?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Microsoft + .pdf","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"\"Microsoft\" + \"pdf\"","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Microsoft AND \"pdf\"","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Microsoft filetype:pdf","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":17,"question":"Which link is not crawlable?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`<a href=\"http://domain.com\">`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`<a onclick=\"newwin('domain.com')\">`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`<a href=\"http://domain.com\" class=\"blue\">`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`<a href=\"../category-2/page\">`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":18,"question":"Which choice represents the best header structure?","code":"markdown     H1: How to Bak Bagels     H2: Ingredients     H3: Dry Ingredients     H4: Wet Ingredients     H2: Instructions     H6: Reviews  markdown     H1: How to Bak Bagels     H1: Ingredients     H1: Dry Ingredients     H1: Wet Ingredients     H1: Instructions     H2: Reviews  markdown     H1: How to Bak Bagels     H2: Ingredients     H3: Dry Ingredients     H3: Wet Ingredients     H2: Instructions     H2: Reviews  markdown     H1: How to Bak Bagels     H2: Ingredients     H4: Dry Ingredients     H5: Wet Ingredients     H6: Instructions     H1: Reviews","choices":[{"text":"markdown\n    H1: How to Bak Bagels\n    H2: Ingredients\n    H3: Dry Ingredients\n    H4: Wet Ingredients\n    H2: Instructions\n    H6: Reviews\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"markdown\n    H1: How to Bak Bagels\n    H1: Ingredients\n    H1: Dry Ingredients\n    H1: Wet Ingredients\n    H1: Instructions\n    H2: Reviews\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"markdown\n    H1: How to Bak Bagels\n    H2: Ingredients\n    H3: Dry Ingredients\n    H3: Wet Ingredients\n    H2: Instructions\n    H2: Reviews\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"markdown\n    H1: How to Bak Bagels\n    H2: Ingredients\n    H4: Dry Ingredients\n    H5: Wet Ingredients\n    H6: Instructions\n    H1: Reviews\n","code":true,"answer":true}]},{"id":19,"question":"All byline dates articles are suddenly no longer visible on a website's listing within Google Search. Assuming no changes have been made to the site programming or content, what is the most likely cause?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"The site has been delisted from Google Search","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The site kept updating the date to make the content appear fresh, without changing the content.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"The articles have aged more than 365 days without any significant updates to the content or the site.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"A Google New sitemap was not provided within 30 days of setting up a Publisher Center account","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":20,"question":"What is an example of a Google search result that can be found in position zero?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Google Ads result","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"featured snippet","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"related searches","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"autocomplete","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":21,"question":"When creating accessible video content, what should you consider including?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"transcript","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"thumbnail","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Flash Player","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"event tracking","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":22,"question":"You are optimizing a website that sells supplies for banking donuts. Which approach is most appropriate to drive more organic traffic?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Buy donutbakingsupplies.com and 301 redirect to your website","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Add the keyword \"donut supplies\" to every page.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Create a new blog with high-quality donut recipes","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Join a link farm to rapidly build inbounnd links.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":23,"question":"Why is it important to be mindful of outbound follow links?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"There is a limit to how many links you can create.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"all of these answers","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Any follow links reduce your PageRank by 1.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Your site's reputation is tied to the sites you link to.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":24,"question":"Which statement is true about JSON-LD?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"It has no relation to JSON.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It is the only structured data format available.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It is considered the most complicated approach to adding structured data.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It is Google's preferred structured data format.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":25,"question":"What is a key reason why duplicate content might cause an issue with ranking?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"It creates an inability to use canonical URLs, which dramatically reduces crawl effectiveness,","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It requires using a 302 redirect, which dilutes PageRank.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It triggers an immediate manual action penalty, which delists an entire domain until the duplicate content is removed.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It makes it difficult for a search engine to determine the original and authoritative content source.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":26,"question":"What attribute would you use to describe the content of an image?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"tabindex","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"longdesc","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"src","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"alt","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":27,"question":"You are researching keywords for a client and creating list for an optimization plan. Which is _not_ a recommended method of creating keyword lists?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"synonyms and related words","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"queries about benefits, features, problems","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"how-to and question-based queries","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"focusing on only high-volume, high-popularity words","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":28,"question":"You want to get a rough idea of how many searches per month a particular search term gets. Which tool do you use?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Google Keyword Planner","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Google Tag Manager","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Google Search Console","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Google Suggest","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":29,"question":"Changing the title tag and/or meta description will have a measurable impact on your _.","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"RSS","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"CTR","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"PPC","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"LSI","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":30,"question":"How do keywords change as people progress through the buying cycle?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"They move from simple to more complex as searchers gather more information and then refine their choices.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"The stay simple, as searchers try to use as few words as possible.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The keywords do not change much at all.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"They move from complex to simple, as searchers find answers to their questions.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":31,"question":"Which technique is an example of black hat SEO?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"cloaking","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"keyword research","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"useful content","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"on-page optimization","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":32,"question":"A local accountant wants to start attracting more business directly from Google organic search. What is the best piece of advice to give to her?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Use the pharse \"local accountant\" as a keyword to focus her website on.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Focus on short-tail keywords.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Register her business with a Google My Business account.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Leave a link to her website in the blog comments of popular accounting websites.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":33,"question":"What is the anchor text in this code sample?","code":"`<a href=\"catalog/gloves.html\">Blue Gloves</a>`","reference":"`<a href=\"catalog/gloves.html\">Blue Gloves</a>`","choices":[{"text":"Blue Gloves","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"href","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"catalog/","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"gloves.html","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":34,"question":"**_** analysis allows you to review requests made to your web server to identify insights such as how ofter a crawler arrives, what pages have 404 errors, and most crawled pages","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Log file","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"HTTP/2","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Cron job","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Resource packet","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":35,"question":"Which page title references content that is evergreen","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Mega List of Teams Going to the Olympics","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Complete Coverage of Microsoft's Latest Announcement","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The Future of SEO in 2020","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"How to Reheat Pizza","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":36,"question":"You load a page and start reading an article, and suddenly the content on the page moves. What metric is used to quantify this impact on user experience?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"First Meaningful Paint (FMP)","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Recalculated Style Timing (RST)","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Latent Loading Signal (LLS)","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS)","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":37,"question":"What is this code is an example of?","code":"<script type=\"application/ld+json\"> {    \"@context\": \"https://schema.org\",    \"@type\": \"Organization\",    \"url\": \"http://www.domain.com\",    \"name\": \"Bradley Corp.\",    \"contactPoint\": {       \"@type\": \"ContactPoint\",       \"telephone\": \"+1-555-555-5555\",       \"contactType\": \"Customer service\"     } } </script>","reference":"```","choices":[{"text":"meta tag","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"HTTP response","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"XML sitemap","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"structured data","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":38,"question":"Which search query would be most difficult to determine search intent?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"XBox live coupon","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Microsoft Office 365","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"LinkedIn login","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"LAX airport directions","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":39,"question":"When you conduct a search, what are the bolded words within the search listing description?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"suggested search terms","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"related search queries","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"keywords that match the search query","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"words with a `<b>` tag assigned in their meta description","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":40,"question":"Which acronym is used to describe the page a user sees after submitting a search?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"SERP (Search Engine Results Page)","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"INDX","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"PARS","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"SEM","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":41,"question":"Which statement is true regarding the use of social signals, such as LinkedIn shares, by Google in its ranking algorithm?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Google does not use social signals to determine rank","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Social signals are identical to backlinks","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Social signals are used to determine topic authority","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Social signals provide a benefit only if they have structured data markup","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":42,"question":"A user clicks an internal link resulting in this redirect chain: `http://domain.com -> https://domain.com -> https://domain.com/`. In this example, what is being consumed unnecessarily?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"redirect allotment","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"crawl budget","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"velocity scale","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"domain authority","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":43,"question":"You are planning for the development of an e-commerce website. Which approach will be more beneficial for rankings?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Optimize the front page of your website to drive traffic from all category search terms.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Optimize product category pages to drive traffic from individual category search terms.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Optimize all pages on the site for all category search terms.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Optimize product pages to drive traffic from individual category search terms.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":44,"question":"You want to block crwlers from accessing your entire website. What robots.txt entry would you use?","code":"User-agent: Allbots     Disallow: *       User-agent: /     Disallow: *       User-agent: *     Disallow:       User-agent: *     Disallow: /","choices":[{"text":"\n    User-agent: Allbots\n    Disallow: *\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"\n    User-agent: /\n    Disallow: *\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"\n    User-agent: *\n    Disallow:\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"\n    User-agent: *\n    Disallow: /\n","code":true,"answer":true}]},{"id":45,"question":"What is the relationship of click depth to PageRank?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"The deeper the click depth, the lower the PageRank","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"PageRank and click depth have no relation","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The deeper the click depth, the higher the PageRank","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Click depth and PageRank are equal","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":46,"question":"What is a popular technique for writing content with the goal of having it appear in a features snippet?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Write the question in a headline tag, and then answer it below in a format that matches the snippet type.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Use the features snippet schema and apply an object that matches the correct snippet type.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Google manually generates featured snippets, so there is no special technique.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Submit the content through Google Search Console, and tag it with the correct snippet type.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":47,"question":"Which approach is not advisable to geotargeting your website?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"using a gTLD with a subdirectory","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"using URL parameters","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"using a gTLD with subdomain","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"using a ccTLD","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":48,"question":"What is a common best practice for handling search result pages on a blog's built-in site search?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Set site research results to no-index.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Do not use site search.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Set site search to 404.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Add a canonical from the search result page to the home page.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":49,"question":"What might help a search engine understand the difference between an article on a dog bark versus tree bark?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"tertiary analysis","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"ranked choice trees","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"semantic analysis","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"knowledge graphs","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":50,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"The title tag was placed within the <HEAD> section of the webpage, but not before the meta content tags, so Google cannot identify the actual title.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The page is using structured data to define an alternative title object, which allows the search engine to pick a preferable version.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"A breadcrumb navigation is in use, which overrides the title tag supplied in the HTML.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Google generated a new title using text on the page that more closely matched the search query.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":51,"question":"What alt attribute should be assigned to an image of a decorative line being used to separate content","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"alt=\"\"","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"alt=\"Thin black line being used to seperate two blocks of content\"","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"alt=\"dec\"","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"alt=\"thin-line\"","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":52,"question":"Your site serves identical content when you visit domain.com/page or domain.com/page?ref=123. What should you implement?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"parameter stripping","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"URL cloaking","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"a 302 redirect","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"a rel=canonical link","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":53,"question":"What data vocabulary is most commonly used when marking up content on a page?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"vocabulary.org","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"RDFa.org","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"schema.org","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"data-vocabulary.org","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":54,"question":"According to Google, what type of content includes topics such as news, legal issues, financial advice, and medical information?","code":"**Explanation:** `Google describes YMYL (Your Money or Your Life) sites/pages as ones that could potentially impact a person’s happiness, health, financial stability, or safety.`","reference":"**Explanation:** `Google describes YMYL (Your Money or Your Life) sites/pages as ones that could potentially impact a person’s happiness, health, financial stability, or safety.`","choices":[{"text":"RSS","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"KYC","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"YMYL","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"BDB","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":55,"question":"When would it be necessary to 301 redirect every page on a site?","code":"**Explanation:** From article: [Types of redirects](https://moz.com/learn/seo/redirection)","reference":"**Explanation:** From article: [Types of redirects](https://moz.com/learn/seo/redirection)","choices":[{"text":"when parameters are used in URLs","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"when migrating from HTTP to HTTPS","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"when launching a new redesign","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"when creating a new subdomain","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":56,"question":"What would contribute to a low bounce rate?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Content does not match search intent.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Page returns 404 error.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Content reflects search intent.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"URL uses parameters.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":57,"question":"What should be as consistent as possible across the web when developing a local SEO strategy?","code":"1. [reference](https://support.google.com/business/answer/7091) 2. [reference #2](https://www.smartinsights.com/search-engine-optimisation-seo/how-to-adjust-your-nap-profile-for-local-seo/)","reference":"2. [reference #2](https://www.smartinsights.com/search-engine-optimisation-seo/how-to-adjust-your-nap-profile-for-local-seo/)","choices":[{"text":"backlinks","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"NAP","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"LRP","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"inbound links","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":58,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"query","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"parser","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"bar","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"link","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":59,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"fresh keyword","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"operative keyword","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"short-tail keyword","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"long-tail keyword","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":60,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Google Input Tools","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"structured data testing tool","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Google Tag Manager","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Google My Business","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":61,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Not only should the blog be on a subdomain, but each of the major navigation areas should be on separate subdomains in order to increase the number and value of the links into the primary domain.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It is best to have the blog on a subdirectory and build links to primary domain.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"It is an advisable choice as it will enable interlinking between the domains and increase the number of links.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The blog should be on a separate URL to avouud building too many links between the same domain or IP.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":62,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"non-indexable","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"irrelevant","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"biased","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"thin","answer":true,"code":false}]}]